As long as I can remember,
I've had hemorrhoids.
And I 've thought for many years,
I shouldn't tell this .
Because hemorrhoids
only grow with Grandpa's .
I thought them to be a
very ungirly thing .
Zinc ointment helps
against the outer itching.
A hazelnut-sized amount
on the finger with the shortest nail.
Then, rub it on the cauliflower,
that proliferates down there .
One can also introduce the ointment anal,
to still the itching on the inside.
My mother has told me,
that it is difficult,
to keep a pussy really clean.
A pussy gets sick
a lot easier than a penis.
That is why hygiene in the bathroom
has the top priority.
Helen, are you ready?
Is everything is fresh again?
Almost.
Come on
Jump.
Trust no one.
Not even your parents.
It' s better to have a scratched knee now,
than to have a broken heart later on.
With a lot of things,
that were taught me,
I do not agree .
So I subjected myself
to a living pusssy
hygiene self-experiment.
At a public toilet
my mother pees
in a floating squatting position.
I take a lot of pleasure from seating
myself fully on the dirty toilet seat .
Then, I wipe the seat clean
with my pussy, in a neat circle.
The dirtier the toilet,
the better.
I' ve done this experiment
for many years,
and I 've never
had a single mushroom .
I have a very healthy
pussy flora.
Hygiene is a lowercase
word to me.
One shouldn' t wash one' s
pussy too much.
My goal is that it can be smelt easily and
seductively right through the pants .
Men will then
percieve this, unconsciously,
because we are all animals so,
who want to mate .
Preferably with people
who smell of pussy.
Are you hungry?
The consistency of the pussy-mucus
plays a major role.
It is always different.
Sometimes like olive oil,
today more like cottage cheese.
Many strongly prefer cottage cheese.
You may not believe me.
But it's true.
Taste alright?
- Can I take a picture of you?
- Now?
Yes.
Thank you.
Looks good.
As if you' re dying.
My sex-souvenir candy .
If you find dicks, sperm and
other bodily fluids disgusting,
it's better just to
leave sex alone.
That, for sure, is not
my intention .
Cooking me something? - Nope,
I just borrowed the vegetables.
That's Toni, my brother.
As a baby he was always
yapping about .
But today he says nothing.
Well, only if you touch his teddy bear .
Stop it now!
Everyone needs hobbies.
For me, besides fucking,
it' s growing avocado trees .
The seeds are my
own little family .
That's mama.
She has tried every religious
and spiritual thing there is.
Hallelujah!
After the divorce
she has gone for the most bizarre religion
of them all.
Catholicism.
Amen !
- Hi.
- Oh, hi . Neighbors.
Great.
- I'm Corinna.
Bye, Corinna.
- Helen, don't be so rude.
It 's not worth it,
get to know us, you know?
Because soon my mother will
wink at the next guy.
And we move away again.
It' s not that bad.
- Still is though.
- Yeah, men are not that easy.
- We need to be off again.
Otherwise my vegetarian
roast will burn.
You can take your
mom over sometimes.
Right.
We' ll invite all of her ex-lovers.
Then we have a really
cozy gangbang evening.
See you soon, take care.
Bye.
Why do you emberass us like that?
What will people think of us?
I have no idea,
what Corinna thought about us.
I just know that she will soon
be my best friend .
And that she had a knack for
always picking the wrong types.
Her last boyfriend was the drummer
in a heavy metal band .
As Corinna would soon find out
the drummer had a very special fondness
during sex .
I love you.
I love you too.
Can you poop on my stomach?
What?
Corinna did her best .
But the worst was that thereafter
everybody knew about it .
Papa?
Can I live with you?
Your eggs are burnt.
Hey,
why don' t you ring the doorbell?
My dad.
He often hurts me a lot,
without realizing it .
To dance so uninhibited
you' ve got
to have a lot of money.
Or a big penis .
Or both, like my father.
As a child of divorce I hope,
as do almost all children of divorce,
for my parents to get back together.
Why?
Because every child loves
his parents unconditionally.
Whether they deserve it or not.
Are you dreaming?
No, I 'm thinking.
Abraham!
- Here I am.
- Take your son, Isaac,
and take him there. as a burnt offering
- Father?
- Yes, my son?
Here is fire and wood.
But where is the lamb,
we wanted to sacrifice?
God will choose the sacrificial lamb,
my son.
What are you thinking about?
How it' ll be when you're old.
Ah yes?
- Uh-huh.
And how would it be?
Good or what?
Do you feel old?
I do not want to talk about it.
Do you understand?
- Uh-huh.
I mean you' re old already,
but I mean really old.
Are you afraid
that I' d die soon?
Do not be afraid.
No. I mean, if you
are old and in need of care.
And I have to wash your ass.
I' d do this at home,
within the family circle.
What do you think?
I find it...
nice. All right.
And her I' d stuff
in a nursing home.
And about me?
I'll lay you down
in the same bed as mom.
Until you die.
You'd tie me to the bed with your
father, until I die?
After all
this man has done to me?
Yes.
How come you want to
punish me like that?
Punish?
Sometimes,
I just have to wait patiently,
it' s in my hands .
Since I really
don't like shaving
I always do it
too fast and too hard .
To me, the ass belongs
to the domain of sex.
So it is subjected to
this modern shaving-duty as well.
Perhaps not everyone knows
what an anal fissure is .
This is a small,
small crack in the anus.
And you can get it easily.
For example, when shaving .
This causes me one of
the greatest pains I 've ever had.
Ahhh ...!
Hello, my sweetheart.
- Hello.
Is everything okay?
Mhm.
Are you sure?
- Uh-huh.
Did you smoke weed?
Okay.
The swollen hemorrhoids
are now pressing full force
against my shaving injury,
and let the fissure
tear ever further .
On the ass-injury, a
bulging blister has formed,
which hangs out of the anus,
like the neck skin
of these tropical birds,
when during mating season
they pump a lot of air into it.
It must look very inflamed.
All who come in say...
Ohh!
I'm Doctor Notz.
Ahhh!
Oh!
- Warn me first, please!
Damn!
What was that?
That was my thumb.
Do you always introduce
yourself like that?
Yes I do, imagine that.
No. First of all, with that thick
bubble in place I can' t see a thing.
And secondly, it presses against
the skin lesions and hurts you.
And now it no longer hurts.
That's quite a success.
So, gentlemen,
what's to be done here?
I think operate,
Professor. - I didn' t ask you yet.
- Rocco.
- I' d suggest it as well.
Surgery? Yes, operate. But right away,
right? Nils?
Definitely.
Have you already eaten
anything this morning? - No.
Eaten nothing, drank nothing?
- No.
Out of sheer pain
I have not eaten anything.
Wonderful, then we apply
general anesthesia . Why? Michael.
- An awkward silence.
- Yes.
Which spares us the everlasting chatter.
Alright then.
We 'll see you later,
looking forward to it, bye.
And whate exactly do you do
in the operating room?
In the OR we cut
the inflamed tissue
around the skin lesion
out in a wedge-shape.
Okay.
- Good.
Can you draw it for me?
I can' t imagine it..
Uh...
So the circle represents your behind.
The circle is my anus.
Oooaaahhh!
You have to
read these documents.
And sign at the end.
It says something about incontinence.
What does that have to do with pee?
This is anal incontinence.
- Never heard of it.
Ah, that means I can no
longer close my sphincter.
And shit will just run right out of me.
- Right.
You' ll need a diaper then.
- Exactly.
But happens relatively rarely.
So, will you sign here?
I can' t really operate
myself at home.
Right, Valerie?
That's right.
That' s where it got me now.
Shit, man.
All the fault of a Ladyshave.
Actually I shave myself
only because of Kanell .
If I had not met him,
this would not have happened .
- Are you shaven?
- What?
Whether you've shaved.
No, why do you ask?
Because I would like to
shave you sometime.
Here is my address.
This is one of my most
spontaneous dates for sures.
So I don' t get callous skin
on my knees.
Want to fuck me now?
But you are too young.
Too bad.
Get dressed.
Helen, hi.
I'm Robin, the nurse.
I've got some news for you,
we' ve managed to plan your
operation real soon.
So, you are operated on the anus,
a very unsanitary place.
Actually, the most unhygienic
of the whole body.
Just the coat, please.
You need to bare it all.
Completely naked?
- Exactly.
Problem?
Yes.
- Why?
I think that's just awful.
They all just talk about
what you look like.
Oh, these are all professionals.
- Yes, of course . Professionals.
I can hear what they're
talking about.
In my subconscious.
Then I' ll go crazy,
in a few years,
and no one knows why.
Uh, the...
the skirt as well.
- Ah.
Yes, it does some patients like that.
Mhm.
Okay.
Excited?
- Yes.
Very good.
What are you writing about?
- A list of my hobbies.
I have to think over,
what I' ll sacrifice to
God non-existent,
so that he' ll spare me
anal incontinence.
Okay.
And what do you want to offer him?
Point 2
Or point 3
Drugs or hookers.
Yes, that's good.
- That's a great sacrifice, I think.
Here's a sedative for you.
This makes the transition to
general anesthesia soft and supple.
Here.
That hit my uvula hard.
Mine is quite sensitive.
I know that from cock sucking.
When they poke real
deep, you know?
Classic.
- Yeah, or something.
Has your girlfriend got
gagging problems as well?
Uh, no, she doesn' t do
oral sex that much.
Too bad.
- Yeah, I thinks so as well.
What do you think so as well?
Nothing.
We are talking about
an undersupply of oral sex.
Aw.
Mhm.
How nice.
Valerie!
Girlfriend?
- Well,
we 're having
a kind of relationship break.
Wow.
For how long?
Two years.
All right.
Here.
So can I call you someone?
Your parents?
No.
My parents died tragically.
Really?
Could these eyes lie?
I think so.
Right.
Very well in fact.
Okay, come over here.
- What is it?
Where is the ball-point pen?
You will call
my parents, okay? - Yes.
That' s dad.
- Yes.
And that's mom.
They have to come
at the same time.
Okay.
- That is important.
Do you understand?
- I promise . - Okay.
United at their daughters bedside.
- Okay.
Look here, it's the foot.
It' s constantly kicking me.
Do you feel that?
Not so hard.
Come on,
the face doesn' t hurt that much.
Have you washed yourself?
Show me your butt.
All right.
This afternoon,
the Dutch city of Enschede.
Was shaken by a huge explosion,
The first reports of the fire at
a fireworks factory
were only vague, yet later
it became a certainty .
Enschede, hours after
the explosion.
Clouds of smoke
still rise in the sky
and give a first impression
of the size of the disaster...
So now it is just as
if we had kissed.
Since it had my spit on it.
Here.
It's better than plastic toys.
At the time there happened to be
a cameraman for the Dutch
Local TV station TV Oost at the site .
His pictures are
a cinematic document.
Of the minutes of terror
that took place.
Nah, too tight for me,
just go over to your mattress.
Ah!
Come here, little one.
After Tonis birth
my parents just argued.
Blow it out, sweetie,
make a wish.
Please let dad back inside.
Tadaa! For you.
The most beautiful thing was the
reconciliation after each battle.
Sometimes you had to
help out a little.
Eventually they didn' t want
to be helped anymore,
and divorced .
And they put me in a boarding school.
But I couldn' t stand it
for too long .
And luckily there were others,
who sorely needed my help.
Okay, then just stick
your finger inside.
And then smell it.
Do it one more time.
Hi.
Make yourself at home.
This is Michael .
The boy Corinna is head
over heels in love with.
Hi.
And Michael has
other advantages .
He pushed
the best grass in town.
Do you have money?
Watch out that he doesn' t
steal anything.
I'll get money.
So, what do you do?
I sell drugs.
Nah, I mean in
your spare time.
I listen to music.
Cool.
Hm
- And...
what do you listen to?
- Minimal.
Uh!
Stop it.
Stop it!
Give me my teddy!
Right now!
Your teddy looks completely torn.
We must bury him, Toni.
No!
Give me my teddy!
You have beautiful breasts.
When I bathe,
I always dive right in.
Mhm.
Everything is warm then.
Hot?
- And quiet.
Somehow one feels so...
sheltered or something.
Like a child.
Like a child?
I would sure like to be
real small again.
Do you?
No.
I don' t know my
way around children.
I've had me sterilized.
And what does your mother say
about that?
She doesn' t know.
It's all gone well.
How can one be so stupid,
as to cut oneself in the ass?
Well, maybe there is
a loving God after all,
and everyone gets the injury,
he deserves.
Is it possible
to see what they cut
away at the surgery?
I do not want
that a part of me ends up in the trash,
with appendixes and abortions.
I 'll ask around
if it's ok.
Did my parents come?
No, I could only reach
their voicemail.
But I told them about the fissure
and the successful OP..
And about the hemorrhoids.
What are you listening to?
Valerie, it's me .
I do not know
whether you'll ever hear this,
but this is for you .
Oh.
What's up?
I've got it.
I'm impressed, nurse Robin.
Where 's my clothes?
They're over here.
Oh.
This is the situation,
mom is so afraid of.
Her absolute nightmare .
My mom thinks
the most important thing for a woman is,
to have clean underwear
in hospital.
But unfortunately you do not know in
advance, when you get to the hospital.
Mamas 's last thoughts
before her death at the scene would be:
How many hours
have I worn my underpants?
Are there any traces yet?
I can gladly
wash it for you if you want.
No. I can wear
them one more week.
Can you call my parents?
You have to order them here.
Tomorrow. At five . It' s important.
Both of them together.
Tomorrow, five o' clock, together.
Here . In this room.
Yes, got it.
If you' re in pain,
simply ring...
I will.
Okay.
Robin?
- Yes?
Thank you.
Don' t be frightened
Light comes on.
It' s a high-fiber diet
for you.
And what if
I have a bowel movement?
The wound will heal
with daily bowel movements,
so that everything expands nicely.
Come on.
One more.
After your bowel movement
you are fired.
So eat it nicely.
Shit.
Sorry.
How can I help you, Helen?
Do you smell something?
Hmm... barely.
Can we speak less formal now?
- Yes, of course.
I need to ask you something.
Yes?
Could you photograph my wound?
My butt hole?
Nope.
- Nope?
That... that's not allowed.
- That's not allowed?
Nope. Well I do not know
if  it is allowed,
but I think
it's not allowed.
But noone has to know
if we do this.
You only have to take your cellphone.
No, my phone is not allowed
in the patients rooms for sure.
But it's not for calling
someone up now is it, Robin.
You do want to photograph
my ass.
Right?
This is really good.
- That's it. I know it.
Here.
That's more hole than ass, man.
I can' t be an ass-model
anymore with that.
I 've never been allowed to see
the wounds of other patients.
Yes?
- Yes . Right.
Now maybe a bit more...
Just take your hand away from there.
So?
- Yes.
Have you had a bowel movement?
- No.
Really?
- Really.
How are we feeling today?
Crappy.
- Crappy?
Yes.
I have a picture
of your masterpiece.
Uh, here.
But as far as I can see the
photo has been made at close range
Yes.
Very close.
Well,
in this routine procedure
there were no complications.
Except for anal incontinence?
You do not know that,
what you're talking about.
Of course, I know that
Anal incontinence? - Yes.
- Is the wound bleeding then?
Nope.
- You see.
So, once you have a bowel movement,
You can go home. Yes?
And that can happen today.
Memel. I am Helen's mom.
- Ah! Excellent. Glad to meet you.
We have just noticed
how wonderful the operation went.
Oh, wonderful! I am pleased.
- I beg to differ, mama.
She's a bit high-strung ofcourse,
your daughter
It's quite normal
in girls at that age.
- Exactly.
- Oh, really?
Yes. don't worry.
We have befriended eachother.
Right? Michael? Yes?
But when you need tips for
bringing her up,
then we will help you.
We have to deal with difficult
personalities more often here.
And you were?
- Professor Dr. Notz.
I am the head doctor of this clinic.
- Ah, yes.
Doctor Notz,
Her mother is perhaps
a difficult personality,
but not my daughter.
If I may give you a hint:
Keep your mouth shut
and do your work.
Bye.
Cede repugnanti!
Cedendo victor abibis.
Give in to the one who defends himself.
In yielding you'll
emerge victorious . Hm?
Now they will all hate
me here . Because of you.
How was the surgery?
Was not there.
It was general anesthesia.
You're too early.
I appointed you at five.
Can you come again after work?
My god, one can' t do
anything right with you.
God again.
Can you take that god
up there down?
No, I can not.
- Still. It bothers me.
Quit that nonsense, Helen.
I can do it myself as well.
No.
All right, I'll do it already!
Careful.
Since when did you have ..
These things there on you?
Hemorrhoids?
Yes.
- Always have.
Not true, I have bathed
you as a baby.
It's been a while.
Yes.
They are hereditary.
The hemorrhoids.
Do you have them, or dad?
- You got them from your father
I got your stuff,
without which you can not even...
Yes. I see it.
There are seven.
That's the second.
I love soft surfaces .
As the greasy leather of
the buck in our sports hall in the past.
But you have to save
these moments for
when nobody notices .
Helen!
What are you doing?
What is that nonsense?
Or so soft
like the glans of a penis .
I really want, ever
since I can remember, to have a child.
But in our family there is a
recurring pattern:
My great-grandmother .
My grandma .
My mama .
And I.
All firstborn .
All girls.
All weak nerves,
disturbed and unhappy.
With my sterilization I
have broken this cycle.
From my tummy
unhappy, disturbed beings
will never crawl out.
Okay! Thank you!
I have brought you
something from America.
The Turduck roast.
You take a quail,
the quail one stuffs into a chicken,
the chicken into a goose
and in the end we have the turkey,
which entirely covers the goose.
Okay.
Oh, it makes me feel queasy in the stomach.
At Helen's birth, the doctors had
to make an episiotomy.
There was a noise
just like this.
And actually...
it looked exactly like
this as well.
It's an organic turkey,
so everyone, even the vegetarians...
Cheers!
You want
me to applaude?
Look,
that's where they've cut.
It's all I wanted to say.
That's where they've cut in.
Ass.
Slugs.
Is this an allusion to my butt hole?
I thought you were interested
in slugs.
You asked me about
them sometimes.
And now I have a whole book.
Yes.
I get tablets for the pain.
What pain?
At my butt.
Ofourse.
What kind of tablets?
- Neoncoloured.
Do you still have an appointment?
No.
You? - I need to
leave you alone again unfortunately.
Hospitals, those are not for me.
I feel myself quite ill.
But you can still
read to me a bit.
It's summer now, everything is dry
and the snail is scared...
dying of heat.
I will read to you gladly.
When I pick you up.
Well, a friendly greeting
to your collegues then.
Which colleagues?
Your work colleagues.
Be well.
- Uh-huh.
Good to see you.
That's good,
I have to tell you something.
I love you.
I will stay with you forever,
even if I do not love you.
It has to be so,
when you have children.
Get well soon.
I've been thinking about your
wound and about your...
...Looseness.
I've talked it over with
a buddy and he told me...
that you're an exhibitionist
or something.
I don' t know how he gets
that idea.
Loving to show, I always say.
Yes. Is that bad?
- Not at all, I...
On the contrary, I would hope
that more girls...
be like this, ehm,
who take the initiative, you know ..
Come a little closer.
Come closer.
Now close your eyes.
What?
Close your eyes.
I 'll tell you a story.
In the street where I live,
is a brothel . The Sauna Oasis.
Guys are always invited for their
18th birthday by their parents.
I was not invited.
So I did everything myself .
Hi.
Any women
who do it with women?
Cynthia!
And I pick one.
Come on.
Put it on the table.
Thank you.
Can I lick you?
Yes.
Did you come?
That went pretty fast alright.
Do you know why I I picked you?
Nope.
Copper roof,
always damp in the basement.
That's what my father always said.
I will give it to her.
These are the residues that they
have cut away from your anus.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
Did you have a bowel movement?
- I do not think so.
And you?
The material in the bag
is highly infectious.
So deal with it accordingly, ok?
Hygiene is paramount
in the hospital.
It's at home with me,
also an important issue.
You know, the sooner you dump,
the sooner we are rid of you, ok?
Do you understand me?
When you're finished playing
with your ass parts
make sure they go
back to the hospital waste.
You've got great eyelashes.
One can't beat natural lashes
like that, right, Mrs. Memel?
Mhm.
You must be proud of your daughter.
Hello, sweetness.
Well then, pleasure to talk to you.
- Yeah.
Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
An old gypsy saying goes,
when one gets too many
compliments for something,
then perhaps it's about to break down.
Look.
Here, for you.
This is all just
a dream, sweetheart.
Go back to sleep.
I'm not sure mama really
did this,
because I often mix up
reality, lies and dreams .
Mainly because of the many drugs,
I've taken .
Michael
left his drugsbox.
And went
off with the real cola.
Do we need to notice him?
A mustache kiss.
Oh, my God.
This one is a bit longer.
Slowly.
Stop.
Hi, this is Michael.
First I, then beep, then you
Oh man, voicemail again.
Here is your favorite Helen.
If you are looking for your Coke can,
uh, we have it.
We have started to drink,
the Coke already. Bye.
Okay, he knows.
Yummy!
Have you actually
ever slept together?
No. He waits for
the right moment . - I see.
Um...
Juhu!
Hey, we were here before.
I think I am completely sober.
I'm cold . Fire!
Debt was the main outcome
of our adventure .
Michael wouldn't talk
to us for a week.
And to appease Michael,
I baptized the rat Michael 2 .
Unfortunately Michael 2 had
left us again soon..
In revenge, I decided
kill her new husband .
But that I would have done
my mother a favor .
What are you doing?
- I'll cover you up, you're very exposed.
Just let it go.
Does't matter what it looks like.
- Then stay like that, in God's name.
Yes.
You're late.
You can leave again.
You're impossible.
I wish that once you
have a daughter,
she acts to you like this
as well, tit for tat.
Then you're in for a long wait.
Why?
Don't you want children?
Can this be thrown out?
Give it to me.
These are the parts
from my ass.
Can you go now?
Can come back tomorrow.
Just go.
And be on time tomorrow.
Valerie...
we only wanted to say to you
that we'd like to thank you
for the last two years
and the 175 night shifts,
you've taken...
Thank you .
And all the best
for your birthday and...
Hello, Spacko.
I need a pizza.
Yes, a spinach pizza and a six pack
At the Hilf... Maria Hilf Hospital.
Room 265 Did you write that down?
All right.
If the pizza is cold,
I'll shove it up your ass.
Corrina is such a good friend of mine,
that we are always get our period at
the same time.
And we made up something
special about that .
Are you ready?
We exchanged our Tampons.
Corinna put my
selfmade one in,
with which I hope to ban the American
Tampon industry .
There it comes, okay?
My blood sister.
Say, do you actually get
those things back out?
Most of the time.
The only small disadvantage
to my homemade tampons is,
that they lack the small
blue filament.
I can't get it out.
- Okay, do not panic.
Ah.
Where was it?
Thank you.
Where are you going?
Hello? I'm talking to you.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Well that took forever.
- Oh, you ordered pizza?
That makes 19 euros.
- So, I 'll give you 12
Helen, shouldn't you eat
high fiber food after surgery?
The prices are not negotiable.
Can you advance me something?
I 'm broke.
What about tipping?
- Say a nice greeting to the kitchen.
Tell them a drunken monkey
could bake a better pizza.
All right.
- Helen Memel is the name.
Fuck me.
- Wow.
Give it to me.
- Mmm.
Give it to me!
- That is proper juicy.
Want some?
No thanks, I've had some.
- Do you want beer?
You know, there simply
are certain rules.
For you or for me?
- Well, for all of us.
For all .
Stop that! Man!
Thank you.
Do you know my pizza story?
- Nope.
You don't?
- Nah, tell me.
That's why I 'm
so soggy with the delivery boy.
Mhm.
Because I want sex.
With very many different men.
At the same time.
- Sounds logical.
First of all . - This story has gone
around for a long time.
Two girls order pizza.
But the pizza doesn't arrive.
And so the girls keep calling
back and complain.
Sometime later, the pizza arrives.
But somehow
the pizza tastes funny.
So the girls bring
the pizza to one ot their fathers,
coincidentially a food chemist.
Still, they all think
the pizza has gone bad or so.
But the analysis tells
a different story.
On the pizza...
is the cum
of four different men.
Well, I imagine the origin
of the story like this:
Our friends are annoyed.
And because the main characters are girls,
they have rape fantasies.
Normal.
So they get their cocks out
and jerk off together on the pizza .
I would like to eat such a pizza.
That would be as if four men
ejaculate directly into my mouth.
Did you ever get an opportunity
like that before?
Uh, rather rare.
Ahh... is delicious.
Good night.
Sleep.
Got my money yet?
I' ve almost shit
my pants, you Spacko.
Corinna and I need the money.
- Corinna and you?
Do you want to move in together or what?
Something like that.
What 's wrong with Michael?
What? Did you finally get
to play on his magic flute?
No.
Could you?
I am pregnant.
Aha.
You know, I 'm looking forward
to it.
I think it's selfish of you.
But that doesn't change a thing between us.
- This changes everything.
And you know it
Do you know why you
have a family like you do?
have no friends?
You stink.
I feel sorry for you.
Get out!
In Helen's birth,
because the doctors had to
make an episiotomy .
makes me feel queasy .
It smells of gas in my room.
I smell nothing.
Maybe not.
It was just a joke.
What is this?
I thought it was boring without you.
Do me a favor
and don't take me for a fool , okay?
No, I get this sometimes.
- But I do not know why.
Good night.
Yeah, fuck you too, Robin.
What?
Nothing.
Fuck you all.
Assholes.
Good day, daughter.
Good day, dad.
Surprise?
A balloon?
A red balloon.
That will make me
better for sure, dad.
No idea what that is?
A hemorrhoid cushion.
You can sit on it,
with no pain.
Did you get this
from the plumbing trade?
Isn't it called the medical trade?
Right.
Your hair is gray.
Well.
Maybe I should leave
you be for now.
Start with the grieving process.
If you're gone then,
everyone will wonder
why I'm so well off.
Sounds reasonable.
What?
- Nothing.
Thanks for inflating it.
I 've got to be
back on the road.
It really is hard
with your schedule.
Yes, work is waiting.
What are you
by profession, dad?
You have no idea, what do I do?
Not exactly, no.
I am an engineer.
Should I also become an engineer?
Yes.
But you're so bad at math
Are you in pain?
I discourage the use of this pillow.
It's for people with
unoperated hemorrhoids,
and if you sit on it,
then everything breaks again.
Is the wouind bleeding?
No.
Then everything is good.
We can dismiss you.
No, I need to stay there,
I still have to have bowel movements.
This pressure on defecation,
brings nothing good.
Try it in peace.
At home.
Can I still stay one day?
No, we only see eachother
if the wound is bleeding.
Well.
Never to be seen again.
I say, good-bye.
Yes? What are you doing?
Holy shit!
I moved a little weird earlier.
Out of my way, please!
Prepare general anesthesia.
Caution! Man!
Robin, you have to
call my parents.
Both, okay?
- Yes.
Tell them what happened.
This is my last chance
to get them here together.
They are preparing
the OR for you right now.
They don't have to clean
it up for me.
I don' t care too much
about order.
Yes. I know.
- So, there you go.
- Robin, I 'm afraid.
Yes, I 'm scared too.
I'm scared for you.
We need to start now,
because you lost a lot of blood.
You may think that you're
still aware of everything,
but this is in reality only a fraction of
of what is going on.
Here we have all
had a bit of bad luck.
Especially you.
Everyone hoped that I' d forget.
But through her silence
it has become ever greater.
Until it has swallowed me.
I have Toni tells everything.
The hardest conversation
I 've ever had to perform .
The did you know?
- I always have this shit dreams.
Where is he?
- I do not know who you mean.
He gave me this thing
over here.
I got it turned on,
but there is nothing on it.
Only noise.
Helen?
Are you laid off?
I've been looking for you.
Yes, I'm just on the way home.
You're lucky that you
still caught me..
You too.
Bacause you can take me to
your home.
You really have to think over
whether that's okay with you.
Yes.
Yes, you still have to think,
or yes, you're okay with it?
If I live with you,
surely you want to sleep with me.
Yes. But for starters,
not in the ass.
Get me out of here.